Contact

adelah@charter.net

www.linkedin.com/in/adelahernandez-b33a164b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing
Patient Safety
Healthcare

Languages

English Spanish

Adela Hernandez

Chief Nursing Officer-CCO/CNO

Fort Worth, Texas

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Strong healthcare services professional skilled in Emergency and Critical Care Nursing, Clinical Research, Nursing Education, Pediatrics, Patient Education, Emergency Management and Healthcare Administration.

Experience

Cornerstone Healthcare Group

1 year 2 months

Chief Nursing Officer-CCO/CNO

October 2019 - Present (10 months)

Lake Charles, Louisiana

Director of Quality Management/ Director of Nursing June 2019 - October 2019 (5 months)

Tucson, Arizona

USMD Health System

4 years 9 months

Emergency Department Nurse Manager

September 2015 - June 2019 (3 years 10 months)

Arlington, Texas

Emergency Registered Nurse

October 2014 - September 2015 (1 year)

Provide full range of nursing care to a diverse patient population that presents to the emergency department with a wide range of medical needs.

Staff Quest

Registered Nurse

January 2014 - October 2014 (10 months)

Registered Nurse Supplemental staff to area hospitals in the Emergency Department and Intensive Care Unit.

Page 1 of 2

Cook Children's Health Care System Emergency Department Registered Nurse November 2013 - April 2014 (6 months)

Texas Health Resources
Registered Nurse Trauma Intensive Care Unit/Charge Nurse
June 2007 - February 2014 (6 years 9 months)
Fort Worth Area

JPS Health Network
Trauma Nurse Clinician
February 2010 - September 2012 (2 years 8 months)

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington
Bachelor of Science in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2004 - 2007)